Preliminary Guide to The Thomas Hahn Chesapeake and Ohio Canal collection, 1939-1993 MS2020
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
- Riley's Lock, No. 24, at Seneca, Md., undated (Box SHARED Box 19, Box 31, Folder 2)
- Cumberland and Pennsylvania Railroad, Cumberland Wharf, with canal boats, undated (Box SHARED Box 19, Box 31, Folder 3)
- Excursion boat "Oak Spring" at the Paw Paw tunnel, C&O Canal, undated (Box SHARED Box 19, Box 31, Folder 4)
- Lock 6 at Brookmont, also called Magazine Lock, undated (Box SHARED Box 19, Box 31, Folder 5)
- Duvall Foundry at Lock 3, used as a veterinary hospital, undated (Box SHARED Box 19, Box 31, Folder 6)
- Boys and captain in canal boat, Lock 42, C&O Canal, undated (Box SHARED Box 19, Box 31, Folder 7)
- C&O Canal scene below Lock 38, Shepherdstown, WV, with the Norfolk & Western Railroad Bridge, undated (Box SHARED Box 19, Box 31, Folder 8)
- Canal boat crossing Seneca Aqueduct, undated (Box SHARED Box 19, Box 31, Folder 9)
- Canal boat Chadakoin, Washington, D.C., C&O Canal, undated (Box SHARED Box 19, Box 31, Folder 10)
- Factory buildings alongside canal in Georgetown, Washington, DC, undated (Box SHARED Box 19, Box 31, Folder 11)
- Riley's Lock, No. 24, at Seneca, Md., in the early 1900s, undated (Box SHARED Box 19, Box 31, Folder 12)
- Canal and lock near Harper's Ferry, undated (Box SHARED Box 19, Box 31, Folder 13)
- Canal Towage Co. boat No. 93 in a lock, undated (Box SHARED Box 19, Box 31, Folder 14)
- Shenandoah at Harper's Ferry?, undated (Box SHARED Box 19, Box 31, Folder 15)
- Canal boat in a lock, undated (Box SHARED Box 19, Box 31, Folder 16)
- Lock, undated (Box SHARED Box 19, Box 31, Folder 17)
- Line of canal boats in canal (Box SHARED Box 19, Box 31, Folder 18)
- Wooden building next to a lock, undated (Box SHARED Box 19, Box 31, Folder 19)
- Wooden building next to a lock with other buildings in the background, undated (Box SHARED Box 19, Box 31, Folder 20)
- Godey Lime Kilns after 1907 with Rock Creek in the foreground, undated (Box SHARED Box 19, Box 31, Folder 21)
- Canal with a house and car in background, undate (Box SHARED Box 19, Box 31, Folder 22)
- Drawing of Shenandoah at Harper's Ferry?, undated (Box SHARED Box 19, Box 31, Folder 23)
- Shenandoah at Harper's Ferry?, undated (Box SHARED Box 19, Box 31, Folder 24)
- View of the Island Vircinius, in the Shenandoah, at Harper's Ferry, undated (Box SHARED Box 19, Box 31, Folder 25)
- Harper's Ferry, undated (Box SHARED Box 19, Box 31, Folder 26)
- Harper's Ferry, undated (Box SHARED Box 19, Box 31, Folder 27)
- Lock with two wooden buildings, undated (Box SHARED Box 19, Box 31, Folder 28)
- Harper's Ferry?, undated (Box SHARED Box 19, Box 31, Folder 29)
- Canal boats on canal with people next to a wooden building, undated (Box SHARED Box 19, Box 31, Folder 30)
- Cushwa Basin, undated (Box SHARED Box 19, Box 31, Folder 31)
- Mules pulling canal boats, undated (Box SHARED Box 19, Box 31, Folder 32)
- Potomac River at Williamsport, MD, undated (Box SHARED Box 19, Box 31, Folder 33)
- View of lock from the canal, undated (Box SHARED Box 19, Box 31, Folder 34)
- Wooden building and in a wooded area, undated (Box SHARED Box 19, Box 31, Folder 35)
- Lock with wooden buildings next to it, undated (Box SHARED Box 19, Box 31, Folder 36)
- Great Falls Tavern?, undated (Box SHARED Box 19, Box 31, Folder 35)
- Aqueduct Bridge and Georgetown from the Virginia bank, c. 1860-1865 (Box SHARED Box 19, Box 31, Folder 38)
- Wharf at Cumberland, MD, undated (Box SHARED Box 19, Box 31, Folder 39)
- Many canal boats in water with buildings in the background, undated (Box SHARED Box 19, Box 31, Folder 40)
- Mules pulling a canal boat, undated (Box SHARED Box 19, Box 31, Folder 41)
- Canal boats on the water with buildings in the background, undated (Box SHARED Box 19, Box 31, Folder 42)
- Aerial view of railroad and canals with buildings in the background, undated (Box SHARED Box 19, Box 31, Folder 43)
- Canal Towage Co. boat No. 93? near wooden building (Box SHARED Box 19, Box 31, Folder 44)
- Boat in lock with buildings in the background, undated (Box SHARED Box 19, Box 31, Folder 45)
- Old lock, undated (Box SHARED Box 19, Box 31, Folder 46)
- Bridge over water with building in background, undated (Box SHARED Box 19, Box 31, Folder 47)
- Seneca Aqueduct(?) with boat and mules on it, undated (Box SHARED Box 19, Box 31, Folder 48)
- Woman standing on Seneca Aqueduct?, undated (Box SHARED Box 19, Box 31, Folder 49)
- Seneca Aqueduct?, undated (Box SHARED Box 19, Box 31, Folder 50)
- Boat on the Seneca Aqueduct?, undated (Box SHARED Box 19, Box 31, Folder 51)
- Seneca Aqueduct?, undated (Box SHARED Box 19, Box 31, Folder 52)
- Canal boat being pulled by mules approaching a lock, undated (Box SHARED Box 19, Box 31, Folder 53)
- Boat on canal next to wooden building (Box SHARED Box 19, Box 31, Folder 54)
- Shenandoah, at Harper's Ferry?, undated (Box SHARED Box 19, Box 31, Folder 55)
- Building with a bridge, undated (Box SHARED Box 19, Box 31, Folder 56)
- Waterway with buildings and bridge, undated (Box SHARED Box 19, Box 31, Folder 57)
- Canal boat and mules on Seneca Aqueduct?, undated (Box SHARED Box 19, Box 31, Folder 58)
- Drawing of different modes of transportation, undated (Box SHARED Box 19, Box 31, Folder 59)
- People in colonial attire, undated (Box SHARED Box 19, Box 31, Folder 60)
- Person in woods with horse, undated (Box SHARED Box 19, Box 31, Folder 61)
- People on water, undated (Box SHARED Box 19, Box 31, Folder 62)
- Canal Towage Co. boat in lock, undated (Box SHARED Box 19, Box 31, Folder 63)
- Cable foot bridge at Great Falls. National Park Service Photo, E.B. Thompson, Historic Negative Collection, ca. 1900-1920 (Box SHARED Box 19, Box 31, Folder 64)
- Canal with buildings in the background, undated (Box SHARED Box 19, Box 31, Folder 65)
- Waterway with buildings in the distance, undated (Box SHARED Box 19, Box 31, Folder 66)
- Lock with stone building, undated (Box SHARED Box 19, Box 31, Folder 67)
- Canal boat in lock with people and a building close by, undated (Box SHARED Box 19, Box 31, Folder 68)
- Shenandoah, Harper's Ferry?, undated (Box SHARED Box 19, Box 31, Folder 69)
- View from water approaching lock, undated (Box SHARED Box 19, Box 31, Folder 70)
- Boats on canal with mules on banks, undated (Box SHARED Box 19, Box 31, Folder 71)
- Ruined lock with a bridge in back, undated (Box SHARED Box 19, Box 31, Folder 72)
- Stone building, undated (Box SHARED Box 19, Box 31, Folder 73)
- Two women on a canal boat, undated (Box SHARED Box 19, Box 31, Folder 74)
- Woman standing next to boat, undated (Box SHARED Box 19, Box 31, Folder 75)
- Canal boat and train with building, undated (Box SHARED Box 19, Box 31, Folder 76)
- Papers from the President's Office of the C&O Canal, undated (Box SHARED Box 19, Box 31, Folder 77)
- Seal of the C&O Canal Company, undated (Box SHARED Box 19, Box 31, Folder 78)
- Girl with mule next to boat, undated (Box SHARED Box 19, Box 31, Folder 79)
- Paper from the Presiden'ts Office of the C&O Canal Company, undated (Box SHARED Box 19, Box 31, Folder 80)
- Drawing with canal boat and train (Box SHARED Box 19, Box 31, Folder 81)
- Alexandria Canal, undated (Box SHARED Box 19, Box 31, Folder 82)
- Alexandria Canal, undated (Box SHARED Box 19, Box 31, Folder 83)
- Railroad station at Great Falls, VA, undated (Box SHARED Box 19, Box 31, Folder 84)
- Paper from President's Office of C&O Canal Company, undated (Box SHARED Box 19, Box 31, Folder 85)
- Great Falls Inn and Iron Foundry ruins, undated (Box SHARED Box 19, Box 31, Folder 86)
- Wooden building amongst trees (Box SHARED Box 19, Box 31, Folder 87)
- View of waterway through cliffs (Box SHARED Box 19, Box 31, Folder 88)
- Wooden building, undated (Box SHARED Box 19, Box 31, Folder 89)
- Lock with buildings on either side, undated (Box SHARED Box 19, Box 31, Folder 90)
- People next to a lock, undated (Box SHARED Box 19, Box 31, Folder 91)
- Canal boats with American flags, building in background, undated (Box SHARED Box 19, Box 31, Folder 92)
- Pontoon Bridge across Potomac River Reslin (Berlin?), October 1862 (Box SHARED Box 19, Box 31, Folder 93)
- Aqueduct or bridge, undated (Box SHARED Box 19, Box 31, Folder 94)
- Flooding with buildings, undated (Box SHARED Box 19, Box 31, Folder 95)
- People at building near canal, undated (Box SHARED Box 19, Box 31, Folder 96)
- Canal with lock and buildings in distance, undated (Box SHARED Box 19, Box 31, Folder 97)
- Papers from Presiden'ts Office of C&O Canal Company, undated (Box SHARED Box 19, Box 31, Folder 98)
- Wooded area, undated (Box SHARED Box 19, Box 31, Folder 99)
- Canal boat in lock, undated (Box SHARED Box 19, Box 31, Folder 100)
- James E. O'Day boat on the water, undated (Box SHARED Box 19, Box 31, Folder 101)
- Drawing of Outlet Incline, C&O Canal, 1876 (Box SHARED Box 19, Box 31, Folder 102)
- Drawing of Ecluse A Plan Incline, undated (Box SHARED Box 19, Box 31, Folder 103)